marugujarat.net 2019-07-05

# Privacy Policy | MaruGujarat.net

https://marugujarat.net is a portal for students and job alert provider platform for simplifying finding job applications and different exam result. This Privacy Policy applies to all the online services provided by https://marugujarat.net. This Privacy Policy describes our practices with respect to you or your company’s personally identifiable information.

This Privacy Policy sets forth the types of personal information collected by us, how we collect and use it and with whom, if anyone, user information is shared. You are advised to please read the policy. By accessing the services provided by https://marugujarat.net, you agree to the collection and use of your data by https://marugujarat.net in the manner provided in this policy. At https://marugujarat.net we are committed to protect your privacy during your visits to our website and recognise our responsibility to hold your information securely and confidentially by https://marugujarat.net.

Information Collected and it’s Use  
Information you provide: Based on the service you use, you might be providing the information such as your name, email address. We may send you ocasional email alerts in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services.  
We may use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customise Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.  
We does make use of log files to find users IP address, Internet Service Provider, Web Browser information and users movement on our website.

Advertise  
We also use third party advertisements on https://marugujarat.net to support our site. When they advertise on our site it may contain cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process. We are working with the ad company Google Adsense Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

Regarding Policy Updates  
We reserve the right to change or update this policy at any time by placing a prominent notice on our site. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting to https://marugujarat.net site.  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, or by means of a notice on our site.

If we decide to make changes in our email practices, we will post those changes to this privacy policy, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate.

Contact MaruGujarat.net  
If you have any queries or concerns about this privacy policy, please free to contact us: info@marugujarat.net
